Standard storage is standard.
标准存储是标准存储
If you have objects that you will access regularly, keep them here.
如果您有将定期访问的对象 请将其保留在此处
Infrequently accessed or IA is a great option
不经常访问或 IA 是一个伟大的选项
for important data that you will use occasionally, but not frequently.
对于您将偶尔使用但不经常使用的重要数据
You access the data in the exact same way,
以完全相同的方式访问数据
but you are charged less for storage and more for accessing the objects.
但对于存储和访问对象的更多信息 您的收费更少
Thus, if you don't access these objects often you will save money.
因此 如果您不经常访问这些对象 那么将节省资金
If you don't know what your access patterns will be for your data,
如果您不知道您的访问模式将针对您的数据
you can use intelligent tiering.
你可以用智能的分层
This automatically moves objects between
这将自动在以下对象之间移动对象 :
standard and infrequently accessed to help you optimize costs.
标准且不经常访问 以帮助您优化成本
Glacier is called glacier to imply
冰川被称为冰川
colder storage or storage that is not as immediately accessible.
较冷的存储器或存储器无法立即访问
This is a good choice for backups or data that you're unlikely to need often.
这是您不太可能需要的备份或数据的好选择
This option is less expensive than standard warmer storage classes.
此选项比标准更温暖的存储类更便宜
Glacier deep archive is even colder storage.
冰川深库是更冷的储藏室
Again, best for items that you need to keep but may never or very rarely access.
同样 对于您需要保留但可能从不或很少访问的项 最好是
This storage tier can take up to 12 hours to give you access to your data,
此存储层最多需要 12 小时才能让您访问您的数据
but again, this tier cost even less.
但这层的成本更低